# JACK MOORE

Patient and caring registered nurse with two years of experience and a Traditional Nursing degree from Jacksonville University. Impeccable care standards and a proven ability to develop and execute efficient and highly-effective nursing care plans. Capable of handling a range of medical issues, including emergencies, care for the elderly, and pediatric cases. Possesses a strong work ethic and dedication to providing first-rate nursing care to all pat ien ts. Excellent com pute r ski lls a n d ad m i n istrative ca pa bi li ties.

8 Short Lane, Jacksonville, Florida, 32256 j ac k. mooregtyou re mail.com (283) 183-4726

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **General Registered Nurse**

Memorial Hospital, Jacksonville, FL January 2020 - February 2020

#### **Pediatric Nurse**

Memorial Hospital, Jacksonville, FL January 2019 - January 2020

- Provided pre and post-operative care to a range of patients, including elderly and pediatric patients
- M o n ito red vi ta I signs of patients i n th e emergen cy depa rtm e nt a n d post-o perative
- Regularly performed blood tests in the phlebotomy department
- Installed IVs and central lines
- Prepared c h a rt notes a nd d evel oped ca re p lans
- Provided immunizations for newborn babies and young children
- ♦ Performed assessments of newborns
- ♦ Installed IVs and performed regular blood tests

#### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor of Science in Traditional Nursing

Jacksonville University, Jacksonville, FI September 2016 - December 2018

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Pediatric care
- Care for the elderly
- · Maternity nursing
- Proven problem-solving capabilities
- IV management
- ♦ Phlebotomy
- Calm and friendly manner
- Excellent time management

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Pediatric Nursing Certification
  Board Certified Pediatric Nurse
- Advanced HIV/AID5 Certified Registered Nurse